Marcel Breuer
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
- Correspondence, 1923-1986, Series 2:; (Boxes 1-6, OV 47; Reels 5708-5717; 5.3 linear feet)
  American Institute of Architects, 1946-1976 (45 letters): membership applications for Edward Larrabee Barnes, Landis Gores, John MacL. Johansen, George Sherman Lewis, A. McVoy McIntyre, Robert Hays Rosenberg, Bernard Rudofsky); a 1963 letter from Breuer's office concerns a Skyscraper Architecture survey team from Japan; a 1968 letter concerns the Comité Organizador de Los Juegos de la XIX Olimpiada
  American Institute of Architects, College of Fellows, 1976 (1 letter): from Breuer's office
  American Institute of Architects, Jury of Fellows, 1960 (3 letters): from Breuer
  American Institute of Architects, Library Buildings Award Program, 1967 (1 letter): from Breuer's office
  American Institute of Architects, New York Chapter, 1945-1963 (16 letters)
  American Institute of Decorators (Richard F. Bach), 1956 (1 letter)
  American Institute of Interior Design in Switzerland (Charles D. Gandy and Susan Zimmermann), 1977-1978 (2 letters)
  American-Jewish Congress: see Commission on Community Interrelations (CCI)
  American Library Association, 1951-1968 (2 letters)
  American Planning and Civic Association, undated: membership notice
  American Press Institute, 1974-1975 (5 letters): from Breuer
  American Radiator and Standard Sanitary Corporation, 1947 (1 letter): from Breuer
  American Shakespeare Festival, 1954 (1 letter): from Breuer's office
  American Society for Church Architecture, 1965-1966 (4 letters)
  American Society for Friendship with Switzerland, 1969 (1 letter)
  American Society of Interior Decorators, 1976 (1 letter): from Breuer's office
  American Society of Planners and Architects (ASPA), 1945-1947 (12 letters)
  Anderson, Lawrence B., 1945-1965 (2 letters): see American Society of Planners and Architects (ASPA)
  András, Ivánka, 1957 (1 letter)
  Andrews, Robert, 1956 (1 letter)
  Aoyagi, Nobuo, 1964 (1 letter)
  Aoyagi, Tetsu, 1965 (1 letter)
  Arbelaez, Carlos, 1952 (1 letter): from Breuer)
  Architects & Engineers Institute, 1959 (1 letter)
  Architects' Collaborative, 1946-1959 (3 letters): see McMillan, Louis and Peggy
  Architectural Association, London, 1965-1969 (7 letters): see project file for UNESCO for correspondence with Edward J. Carter Architectural Design, 1960 (1 letter): from Ernesto Fuenmayor and Manuel Sayago of Centro Profesional del Este)
  Architectural Forum, 1960 (1 letter): from Leonard J. Currie
  Architectural Group, (W. D. Wilson), 1947 (1 letter)
  Architectural League of New York, 1947-1975: (26 letters and minutes from 6 meetings): see Ketchum, Morris
  Architectural Record, 1946-1959 (9 letters)
  Architectural Students Association, 1958 (1 letter)
  Architecture Formes Fonctions, 1971 (3 letters): includes a typescript "Design Research in Concrete" for July 1971 magazine
  Architektur + Wohnwelt, 1975 (3 letters)
  Argan, Giulio Carlo, 1955-1957 (6 letters)
  Arizona, University of, 1974 (1 letter): from Breuer's office
  Arnold, Randolph, undated: illustrated Christmas card
  Arp, Hans Jean, 1954-1959 (5 letters): a 1959 letter on Arp's behalf from Marguerite Hagenbach; a 1959 wedding announcement for
  Arp and Hagenbach
  Arseniev, Milko, 1975 (1 letter)
  Art Circus: see Long Beach Art Association, Inc.
  Art Directors Club, Inc., 1975 (5 letters)
  Artek-Pascoe (Clifford Pascoe), 1941-1946 (2 letters)
  Artigas, Josep Llorens (ceramist colleague of Joan Miró), undated and 1960-1963 (5 letters)
  Arts Council of Great Britain, 1962 (4 letters): concern an
  Alexander Calder sculpture
  Art Squad, Inc. (Ernest Costa), 1952 (1 letter): from Breuer's office
  Asfia, H. E. Dr. Safi (Iranian deputy prime minister), 1974 (1 telegram): from Breuer
  Ashihara, Yoshinobu ("Yosh"), undated and 1954-1970 (26 letters): a 1955 letter encloses a photograph of Ashihara and a model of his project
  Association of Hungarian Students in North America, undated and 1958 (4 letters)
  Atelier International, Ltd., 1968 (2 phone messages)
  Atkin, William Wilson (Silvermine Publishers), 1965 (1 letter)
  Atlanta Central Library, 1975 (1 letter): from Breuer
  Atlantic Refining Company, Inc., 1956 (1 letter)
  Atlas Tile & Marble Company, 1955 (1 letter): from Breuer's office
  Auchincloss, Lily and Douglas, undated and 1963 (5 letters)
  Auckland University College, 1945 (2 letters): 1 letter from Walter Gropius
  Aufricht, Gustave and Maria, 1955-1970 (4 letters)
  Aujame, Roger and Edith (and María Feuyo McVitty), undated (1 letter)
  Australian National Gallery, Canberra, 1975 (3 letters): from Breuer
  Austrian Consulate General, 1951 (2 letters)
  Austrian Institute and Mrs. Schlag, 1964 (invitation to reception)
  Auzelle, Robert (architect), 1956 (1 letter): see Académie d'Architecture
  Babarovic, Gretchen and John, undated and 1963 (2 letters)
  Bacal, Jacob, 1967 (1 letter)
  Bachem, Hans Peter (architect), 1950 (1 letter)
  Baer, David C. (AIA), 1956 (1 letter): from Breuer
  Bak, Joseph, 1950 (1 letter)
  Baker, James (Tower Development), 1981 (1 letter): from Breuer's office
  Baldes, Jeannette, 1948 (1 letter)
  Baldwin, Benjamin, undated (2 letters)
  Ballard, Robert F. R., 1975 (1 letter): from Breuer's office
  Bard Civic Award Trust Fund: see City Club of New York, Albert S. Bard Civic Award Trust Fund
  Bárdos, Tamés, 1947 (1 letter): from Breuer
  Barnes, Belva Jane ("B. J."), undated and 1956-1957 (4 letters)
  Barnes, Edward Larrabee (architect), 1945-1955 (5 letters)
  Barnett, Steven G., 1966 (1 letter)
  Barroso, Nicolás Mariscal (VIII Congreso Panamericano de Arquitectos, México), 1952 (2 letters)
  Barry, Gerald, 1951 (1 invitation): mentions Barry
  Bartholdy & Klein, 1933 (1 letter)
  Bartlett, Allan J., 1950 (1 letter): from Robert W. Gumbel
  Bartolozzi, Goffredo (Vetro Italiano di Sicurezza, Milan [VIS]), 1959 (1 letter)
  Bassetti, Fred (Bassetti & Morse, Architects), 1951 (2 letters)
  Bauen + Wohnen, 1974-1975 (5 letters): from Breuer
  Baughman, George F. (New York University), 1959 (1 letter)
  Bauhaus-Archiv, Bibliothek und Schausammlung, 1972 (1 letter): to Knoll International
  Bauhaus Archiv E. V., 1960 (1 letter)
  Bayer, Herbert and Joella, undated and 1933-1966 (87 letters)
  Beaux Arts Club, 1968 (1 letter)
  Beaux-Arts Institute of Design, 1946-1947 (3 letters)
  B.E.B. Consultants, 1982 (1 letter): from Robert F. Gatje
  Bechtol, Ron (Lance Larcade & Bechtol), 1968-1976 (3 letters)
  Beck, Martin (New York University), 1962-1964 (2 letters): from Hamilton Smith
  Beckhard, Herbert and Ellie and Susan, undated and 1954-1980 (45 letters)
  Bee, Anton, 1957 (1 letter)
  Beekman, Rev. Gerardus, 1955 (1 letter): from Breuer
  Begrow, Harold J., 1954 (3 letters)
  Behar, Esther, 1968 (1 letter): from Breuer
  Belgiojoso, Lodovico (Lodovico B. Belgiojoso, Enrico Peressutti, Ernesto N. Rogers, architects), 1950 (1 letter)
  Belluschi, Pietro (MIT School of Architecture and Planning), 1954-1968 (3 letters)
  Bemis, Frances, 1954 (1 letter)
  Bemo Shipping Company, 1954-1956 (2 letters)
  Bender, Richard (Harvard University), 1952 (2 letters)
  Benesch, Edward M. (Gomprecht & Benesch), 1955 (1 letter)
  Benglia, Christine (architect; married architect Alistair Bevington), 1964 (1 letter)
  Bennett, Richard M. (Loebl, Schlossman & Bennett), 1958 (1 letter)
  Benton & Bowles, Inc., Advertising, 1955 (1 letter)
  Beothy, E., undated (1 letter)
  Bergen County Cut Stone Company, 1967 (1 letter): from Breuer's office
  Bergen, Emiel, 1956 (1 letter)
  Berger, Donald (North Dakota Agricultural College), 1953 (1 letter)
  Berger, George, 1950 (1 letter)
  Berger, Otti, undated and 1934-1937 (7 letters)
  Berger, Sanford and Helen (architects), 1945 (1 letter): from
  Breuer to László Moholy-Nagy and Ludwig Mies Van der Rohe introducing the Bergers
  Berger, Stephen E., 1959 (1 letter)
  Berizzi, Sergio, 1959 (4 letters): letters of introduction
  Berko, Franz, 1946-1947 (5 letters): including one from László Moholy-Nagy
  Berlin Interbau, (International Building Exhibition), 1957 (1 letter): from mayor of Berlin
  Berndt, Marianne, 1933 (1 letter)
  Berti, Vincent, 1974 (1 letter): from Breuer's office
  Better-Philadelphia Exhibition (Richard A. Protheroe, Harry
  B. Nason, Hugh B. Sutherland), 1947 (1 letter)
  Bevington, Alistair M., 1959 (1 letter): includes résumé
  Bevington, Mariette (stained-glass designer), 1967 (1 letter): to Herbert Beckhart
  Bharadwaj, Ajaya, 1955 (2 letters)
  Biasini, E. J. (French prime minister), 1972 (1 letter)
  Biddle, Mrs. Francis, 1962-1968 (3 letters): includes a funeral announcement for her husband)
  Biddle, George, 1965 (4 letters): 3 from Breuer
  Bier, Justus (University of Louisville), 1938 (3 letters)
  Bigeleisen, Jacob (University of Rochester), 1970 (1 letter) Ronald S. Biggins and Associates, 1958 (1 letter)
  Bijenkorfbeheer N.V., Amsterdam, 1967-1974 (2 letters): from Breuer
  Bill, Alexander H., Jr., undated (1 calling card)
  Blake, Peter (architect), undated and 1950-1976 (41 letters): a 1958 letter from Breuer is illustrated with a hand-drawn map by
  Blake of Easthampton property
  Blanton, John A., 1951 (1 letter)
  Blaustein, Morton K., 1963-1965 (2 letters)
  Bliss, Douglas P. (Glasgow School of Art), 1947 (1 letter): from Breuer
  Bloeme, Sidney, 1963 (1 memorandum): from James S. Plaut
  Blum, Kurt (photographer), 1974 (1 letter): from Breuer's office
  Bode, Paul (architect), 1956 (1 letter)
  Bodri, Ferenc, 1967-1975 (3 letters): 2 1975 letters from Breuer
  Boehringer Ingelheim, Ltd., 1975 (1 letter): from Breuer
  Bogner, Walter, 1938-1960 (4 letters): see Project File for UNESCO
  Boissonnas, Eric and Sylvie, undated and 1960-1978 (20 letters)
  Bollingen Foundation, 1964 (1 invitation): to reception in honor of Sigfried Giedion
  Bonaparte, Mrs. Robert L., 1955 (1 letter)
  Bonomi, Maria, undated and 1958 (2 letters)
  Bookman, Mrs. John, 1964 (1 letter)
  Borbíró, Virgil (Hungarian architect), 1945-1956 (2 letters): includes Borbíró's obituary
  Borglum, Paul, 1950 (1 letter): see Project File for UNESCO
  Born, Karl, 1968 (1 letter): from Breuer
  Borsódy, István ("Stephen"; historian; Hungarian Legation) and Zsóka, 1946-1965 (5 letters): 1951 letter includes a biographical sketch of Borsódy by Aladár Szegedy-Maszák
  Bortfeldt, Hermann (Büro Willy Brandt), 1963 (1 letter)
  Bosch, Robert, 1934 (2 letters)
  Bosserman, Joseph Norwood, 1963-1967 (2 letters)
  Bosshard, J., 1956 (1 letter)
  Boston Architectural Center, 1968 (1 letter)
  Boston Redevelopment Authority, 1970 (1 letter)
  Boston Society of Architects, 1946 (1 letter): from Breuer to John R. Abbott
  Botond, Stephen G. ("Pista"; architect), 1958-1960 (2 letters): includes wedding announcement for Botond and Patricia Potter Luce
  Bouchet, Maxime, 1953 (5 letters)
  Bourget, Inc., 1955 (2 letters): from Breuer's office
  Bower, John, 1954 (1 letter)
  Bozzola, Vittorio, 1964 (2 letters)
  Bradford, Carol (Mrs. Amory H. Bradford), 1951 (1 letter): from Breuer
  Brandon-Jones, John, 1958 (1 letter)
  Brandstätter, Elsbeth, 1936-1937 (2 letters)
  Brassaï, Gyula Halász (Romanian photographer), undated (1 calling card): no signature
  Peter Bratti Associates, 1974-1975 (2 letters): from Breuer
  Bratti, Peter (A. Tozzini Tile Works, Inc.), 1958 (1 letter)
  Braun, Wolfgang, 1968 (1 letter): from Breuer
  Braziller, George, 1966 (1 letter)
  Bremer, Paul and Nina, 1975 (2 letters)
  Breuer, Constance (née Leighton), 1947-1982 (22 letters): from Breuer and Breuer's office; a 1967 letter, 1967, from French filmmaker Gerard Calisti is routed from Robert Osborn; an invitation from M. Knoedler and Company concerns reception for Lina Kandinsky
  Breuer, Francesca, undated and 1966-1973 (3 letters): includes a letter of recommendation from Tician Papachristou
  Breuer, Hermina, 1950 (1 telegram): from Breuer
  Brewer-Cantelmo Company, Inc., 1966 (3 letters): from Breuer's office
  Brewer, Joseph, 1965 (1 letter)
  Brewster, George W. W., Jr., undated and 1946 (2 letters)
  Brey, David M. (architect), 1950 (1 letter)
  Breydert, Katherine, 1946 (1 letter)
  Brickel/Eppinger, Inc., 1963 (3 letters)
  Brigham, Richard C., 1954 (1 letter)
  Brion, Maud (secretary to Eric Cercler), 1966-1972 (10 letters)
  Brissenden, Norine (Mrs. P. R. Brissenden), 1947 (1 letter)
  British Chair Company, 1954 (1 letter): from Breuer's office
  Brodovitch, Alexey (Harper's Bazaar), 1954-1961 (16): 13 letters from Breuer's office
  Broner, Gisela (wife of Erwin Broner, architect), undated (1 letter)
  Brooklyn College Library, 1958 (1 letter)
  Brooklyn Museum, 1944 (1 letter)
  Brooks, J. H. (Putnam & Company), 1954 (1 letter): from Breuer
  Brooks, Kenneth, 1968 (2 letters)
  Brown, Elliott, 1951 (4 letters)
  Brown, Graham, 1954 (1 letter)
  Brown, Helen M., 1958 (1 letter): from Breuer's office
  Brown, Jane M. (Mrs. Elliott Brown), 1975 (1 letter): letter is illustrated with drawing of Alexander Calder mobile
  Brown, Joseph, 1955 (1 letter): includes transcript of
  Brown's lecture at Princeton University
  Browne, Robert Bradford (architect), 1968 (1 letter)
  Brumwell, Marcus, 1944 (1 letter)
  Brun, Jacques D. (architect), 1958 (1 letter)
  Bryn Mawr School for Girls, 1981 (1 letter): from Betsy Prioleau
  Bryson, Clayton J., 1950 (1 letter)
  Budapest Muszaki Egyetem (István Benke), 1970 (1 letter)
  W. S. Budworth and Son, Inc., 1963 (1 letter): from Charles H. Sawyer
  Builders Publishing Company, 1954 (1 letter): to Rufus Stillman
  Building Progress, 1974 (1 letter): from Breuer's office
  Bujdosó, Ferenc, 1963 (2 letters)
  Bulova, Arthur, 1950 (1 letter): from Breuer's office
  Burchard, Charles (architect), 1945-1960 (10 letters)
  Burchard, John E., 1967-1971 (2 letters): see American Society of Planners and Architects (ASPA)
  Burkland, Howard (Shere Naven Corporation), 1951 (1 letter): from Stamo Papadaki
  Burton, Véra, undated (1 letter)
  Buyoucos, James V., 1952 (1 letter): from Breuer
  Byrd, Dale, 1950-1968 (5 letters)
  Cabinet Norbert Guerle, 1953-1954 (10 letters)
  Caesar, Harry I. (Leslie Stillman's father, married to sculptor Doris Caesar), 1954-1955 (4 letters): 3 from Breuer's office
  Calder, Alexander, 1938-1975 (12 letters): a 1947 letter is illustrated with a map; a 1975 letter contains a typescript about
  Calder
  Calico Museum of Textiles, India, 1974 (1 letter): from Breuer's office
  California Council, AIA, 1960 (5 letters)
  California, University of, Berkeley, 1957-1964 (3 letters)
  Calisti, Gerard (French filmmaker): see Breuer, Constance
  Canaday, John (New York Times), 1959 (1 letter): from Rufus Stillman
  Canadian Architect, 1974 (1 letter): from Breuer's office
  Canavesi, Schifra, undated and 1935-1957 (8 letters)
  Candela, Felix (Cubiertas ALA S.A.) and Dorothy, undated and 1956 (3 letters)
  Caplan, Frank (Creative Playthings), 1950 (1 letter)
  Cardinal Stritch College, Milwaukee, Wisconsin, 1970 (1 letter)
  Cardot, Vera (photographer), 1975 (1 letter): from Breuer's office
  Carmel, Moty, 1968 (1 letter): from Breuer
  Carpanelli, Franco, 1951 (1 letter)
  Carpentier, Jacques H., 1960 (1 letter)
  Carré, Louis, 1964 (1 letter and 1 picture postcard): postcard shows map to Maison Carré and house designed by Alvar Aalto
  Carreras, Guillermo and Margarita, 1968 (1 letter): from Breuer
  Carson, Alice Morgan (Museum of Modern Art), undated and 1943 (3 letters)
  Carstensen, William (Carstensen, Inc.), 1954 (1 letter): from Breuer's office
  Carter, Edward J. ("Bobby"; librarian, UNESCO): see, Architectural Association, London; see Project File for UNESCO
  Carter, Stephen Newhall, 1976 (1 letter)
  Cassinello, F. (Instituto Tecnico de la Construcción y de Cemento), 1960 (1 letter)
  Catalano, Eduardo Fernando, 1945-1968 (8 letters)
  Catan-Rose Institute of Art, 1965 (invitation): to reception at Gracie Mansion
  Cavazzuti, Ugo, 1969-1970 (2 letters)
  Central Mortgage and Housing Corporation, 1975-1976 (3 letters): from Breuer's office
  Central School of Arts and Crafts, London, 1947-1950 (2 letters): includes an invitation to the school's presentation of diplomas by Sir Kenneth Clark
  Central State AIA Conference, Omaha, 1976 (1 letter): from Breuer's office
  Century Association, 1976 (1 letter)
  Century Club, 1974-1976 (3 letters): 2 letters from Breuer's office
  Century Lighting Company, 1956 (1 letter): from Breuer's office concerning Torrington, Connecticut factory
  Cepero, Carlos Celis (architect), 1965 (1 letter)
  Cercle d'études Architecturales, 1953 (1 letter)
  Cercler, Eric: see Brion, Maud
  Chase Manhattan Bank, 1955-1965 (5 letters): from Breuer's office
  Chatfield, Ayla K. (architect), 1975 (2 letters)
  Checkman, Louis (photographer), 1955 (1 letter)
  Cheever, John, 1967 (1 letter)
  Chelsea Association for Planning and Action, 1941 (1 letter)
  Cheng, Tzu-tsai, 1968 (1 letter): from Breuer
  Chermayeff and Cutting, Architects and Industrial Designers, 1956 (2 letters)
  Chermayeff, Ivan, 1957-1975 (2 letters): from Breuer's office; a 1957 letter concerns a 70th birthday greeting for Le Corbusier
  Chermayeff, Serge (Erich Mendelsohn & Serge Chermayeff, Architects), 1936-1978 (10 letters)
  Cherry, Ned, 1968 (1 letter): from Breuer
  Chiang, Helen and Arthur, 1950 (envelope only) and 1970 (1 letter)
  Chicago Housing Authority, 1946 (2 letters)
  Chien, Alan Shue Shih, 1969 (2 letters)
  Children's Recreation Foundation, Inc., 1967 (1 letter): from Breuer's office
  Chinoy, Rustam, 1954 (1 letter): from Breuer's office
  Churchill, Henry S. (Churchill-Fulmer Associates), 1947 (1 letter): from Breuer
  Ciampi, Mario J. (architect), 1968 (1 letter)
  Cidor, Ruth, 1971 (1 letter)
  Citizens Committee for a Nuclear Test Ban Treaty, 1963 (1 letter): see also Van Doren, Mark
  City Club of New York, 1963-1964 (3 letters)
  City Club of New York, Albert S. Bard Civic Award Trust Fund, 1968 (6 letters)
  Ciudad Universitaria de México, 1952 (1 invitation): to VIII Congreso Panamericano de Arquitectos
  Clark, Donald and Dallas (Associated Seed Growers), 1954 (1 letter): see Project File for UNESCO
  Clarke, Arundell, 1950 (1 letter)
  Clergue, Lucien (photographer), 1966-1967 (5 letters)
  Cleveland Museum of Art, 1967 (1 letter): from Breuer's office
  Cleveland Trust Company, 1970 (1 letter)
  Clyne, Harry, 1947 (1 letter): from Breuer
  Cochran, Alexander S. (architect), 1950-1967 (4 letters)
  Coderch, J. A. (architect), 1961 (1 greeting card): includes photograph of exhibition
  C. Coggeshall Design, 1944 (3 letters)
  Cohen, Ken, 1968 (1 letter): from Breuer
  Cold Spring Granite Company, 1960-1965 (11 letters): a 1964 letter has a design for a candle holder
  Cole, Howard I. (Rutgers University), 1957 (1 letter): from Breuer
  Coleman, Albert, 1945 (1 letter)
  Colen, Eszter and Bruce, 1963 (2 letters)
  Colorado, University of, Boulder, Student Chapter of AIA, 1958 (1 letter)
  Columbia Broadcasting System (CBS), 1975 (1 letter): from Breuer's office
  Columbia University, 1964-1977 (6 letters): see Project File for UNESCO
  Comité Français de l'American Field Service, 1956 (1 letter)
  Comité Organizador de Los Juegos de la XIX Olimpiada, 1968 (4 letters)
  Commission on Community Interrelations (CCI) of the American-Jewish Congress, 1945 (8 letters)
  Compagnie Française de Transports Internationaux, 1954 (1 letter)
  Compton, W. Danforth, 1950 (1 letter)
  Concha, Gonzales, 1952 (1 letter): from Breuer
  Concrete Industry Board, Inc., 1969 (2 letters)
  Condé Nast Publications, Inc., 1955 (1 letter)
  Congrès Internationaux d'Architecture Moderne (CIAM),
  Chapter for Relief and Post-War Planning, 1944-1956 (27 letters)
  Congrès Internationaux d'Architecture Moderne, Mars Group (British branch of CIAM), 1946-1947 (5 letters)
  Conklin, George W. (architect), 1956 (2 letters)
  Connecticut Chapter of AIA, 1963 (2 letters)
  Connecticut Public School Building Commission, 1951 (1 letter): from Breuer
  Connecticut Society of Architects (Norman L. Raymond), 1963 (1 letter)
  Contemporary Arts Association, 1952 (2 letters)
  Contemporary Arts Center, 1965 (3 letters): concerning Josef Albers exhibition
  Contemporary Authors, 1963 (1 letter)
  Contini, Paolo and Jeanne, 1968 (1 letter)
  Contreras, Carlos (XVI Congreso Internacional de Planificacion y de la Habitación, México), 1938 (2 letters)
  Conway, Harvi, 1968 (1 letter): from Breuer
  Cooke, Maymay (Mrs. Francis Cooke), 1947 (1 letter)
  Coolidge, Frederic S. and Anne, 1947 (1 letter)
  Cooper-Hewitt Museum of Design, 1975 (2 letters): from Breuer
  Cooper Union, 1958 (2 letters)
  Cooper, Wyatt Emory, undated (1 letter): mentions Eugene J. McCarthy
  Corcoran, Kostelanetz, Gladstone & Lowell, 1959 (1 letter)
  Cordos, Stephan, undated (1 letter)
  Corkran, D. C. (Charles F. Orvis Company), 1944 (5 letters)
  Cornigliano S.p.A. ("Società per Azioni"; limited company which installs exhibitions), 1958 (3 letters)
  Corson, Richard A., 1950 (1 letter)
  Coulson, Anthony J., 1975 (1 letter): from Breuer
  County Roofing Company, 1957 (1 letter)
  Crampton, Nancy (photographer), 1975 (1 letter)
  Creighton, Thomas H., 1950 (1 letter): written with Katherine Morrow Ford
  Crohn, Norma and Richard, 1968 (1 letter)
  Croll, Jean, 1939 (1 letter)
  Cromley, Don, 1968 (1 letter): from Breuer
  Crotin, 1934-1935 (5 letters)
  Crowther, J. G. (author) and Fransiska, 1936 (2 letters)
  Csernyei, Zsuszi, 1939 (1 letter)
  Cuevas de Vera, Adela ("Tota"), 1933-1934 (7 letters)
  Cunningham, Allen, 1957 (1 letter)
  Currie, Leonard (architect), undated and 1944-1978 (29 letters): see Architectural Forum
  F. B. Curry Company (Frank B. Curry), 1945 (3 letters)
  Cushing, Tom, 1937 (3 letters)
  Cutler Farm (Lily C. Johanson), 1951 (1 letter)
  Cutler, Robert W., 1968 (1 letter)
  Czike, Dr. Gyuláné, 1957 (3 letters)
  Dach, Joseph, 1944 (1 letter)
  Daidone, Anthony J., 1958 (1 letter)
  Damora, Robert (photographer), 1955-1967 (3 letters)
  D'Andrea Brothers, Inc., 1957 (1 letter)
  Bernard Danenberg Galleries, 1974-1975 (3 letters): from Breuer
  Danielsson, Lars (Swedish architect), 1956 (3 letters)
  D'Arcy, Frank (architect), 1957 (1 letter)
  Dauber, Deanna L., 1975 (2 letters)
  Daurel, Paul (architect), 1970 (1 letter)
  Davenport, Keith H., 1946 (1 letter)
  Daves, L. Joan, 1951 (1 letter)
  Davis, Arthur, 1946 (1 letter): from Breuer
  Davis, Brody, Chermayeff, Geismar, deHarak, Associates, 1969 (2 letters)
  Davis, Columbus, 1946 (1 letter)
  Davis, Paul (photographer), 1955 (1 letter): from Breuer
  de Bever, Leo J., 1958-1960 (2 letters)
  de Bodard, Connie, 1956 (1 letter)
  De Carli, Carlo (Politecnico Milano), 1968 (1 letter)
  Decima Triennale di Milano, 1954 (1 letter)
  Decker, H. Carlton (architect), 1968 (1 letter): concerns Interama
  DeCoene, Pierre, 1966-1968 (2 letters)
  Dedet, Dr. Jacques (and Mme. Georges Cexier, Mme. Pierre
  Dedet, Mme. André Laurenti), undated (1 letter)
  De Hausner, Mrs. Djin Lilli S., undated and 1935-1936 (11 letters)
  Deimel, Klöckner, Koebel, 1959 (1 letter)
  Del Buttero Enzo (Vetro Italiano di Sicurezza [VIS], Milan), 1959 (1 letter)
  De Leu Dulles, Mrs. J., undated (1 letter)
  Delft Student Debating Society "Vrije Studie," 1957-1958 (6 letters)
  DeMars, Vernon (DeMars and Wells), 1967 (1 letter)
  Democratic National Committee, 1960 (1 letter)
  De Rivera, José, 1946 (1 letter)
  Derome, Leon, 1953 (1 letter)
  Deschamps, Julio, 1950 (1 letter): includes 4 photographs of a house under construction
  design magazine, 1975 (1 letter): from Breuer's office
  Design Quarterly, 1976 (1 letter): from Breuer's office
  Design Research, 1965 (2 letters)
  de Spirlet, André (Cie. Belge de Chemins de Fer et d'Enterprises), 1963 (1 letter)
  Dévényi, Iván, undated (1 letter)
  De Vries & Company, 1953 (1 letter)